We were in a store and a guy in that store...
我们那时候正坐在商店里有个人进来
...told us to put our uniforms on.
就叫我们去参军
"what the hell are you talking about? "
"你到底在说什么? "
He says, "The USA is in a war with Japan."
他说: "美国与日本开战了"
We couldn't believe it.
我们压根儿就不敢相信
Well, our country was attacked.
我们的国家被攻击了
It's different.
这是不同的
It wasn't like Korea or Vietnam.
这与朝鲜战争或越南战争不同
We were attacked.
我们被攻击了
And, you know, it was a feeling that...
你知道 这种感觉...
...maybe, we're just dumb country people but...
或许我们是乡下老实人
...where I come from a lot of us volunteered.
但我们很多人都自愿参军
"Who would like to volunteer for the Tank Corps?
"谁要自愿加入坦克部队? "
"Who would like to volunteer for the Air Force?
"谁要自愿加入空军? "
"Who would like to volunteer for the Navy? " or whatever.
"谁要自愿加入海军? "
And then, they said:
他们又说
"Who would like to volunteer for the Airborne? "
"谁愿意加入空降师? "
Somebody says, "What the hell's the Airborne? "
什么是"空降"啊?
Nobody ever heard of it.
根本没有人听过
We came from a small, small town.
我们来自一个很小的城镇
And three fellows in that town that were 4F...
镇上有三个人因为体检不合格而自杀
...committed suicide because they couldn't go.
因为他们不能从军
A different time.
真是个不同的年代
I did things.
我们做了些事
I didn't do them for medals.
我们做那些事不是为了勋章
I didn't do them for accolades. I did 'em because it's what had to be done.
我们做那些事不是为了荣誉 我们做那些事只因那是必须做的事
The guy says, "would you jump out of airplanes?
有人说: "各位 当你跳出飞机...
"You know, you got all your army equipment...
"你带着所有陆军给你的配备...
"...and you jump out of airplanes, to fight the enemy."
"跳出飞机 准备与敌人作战..."
These guys, they said, "Go to hell."
我们说"去死吧"
Nobody put up their hands.
没有人举起手
And then, I don't know what it was brought it up...
我不知道是谁提起的
...but the guy giving the speech was saying:
但有个人演讲提到
"But you get paid $50 a month more."
"你一个月可以多赚50块钱"
So, that made it a hundred bucks.
所以那就是100块
I want a whiff of chicken pie.
...我真想来块鸡肉馅饼
Okay, boys, let's get this gear stowed.
弟兄们 把装备都收好
Fox Company...we go in five.
Ｆ连 我们五分钟内出发
"In the name of the Father..."
以圣父圣子之名
1st Platoon, draw small arms.
第一排准备好轻武器 敌人到了再准备就晚了
Do you need a hand, Lieutenant?
需要帮忙吗 中尉?
Easy Company! Listen up!
Ｅ连注意! 整装!
Gather up around me.
朝我靠拢集合
Just move it up. Come on, gentlemen.
动作快 大家快点
Let's go!
快点!
Now, the Channel coast is socked in with rain and fog.
现在英伦海峡笼罩在雨雾之中
High winds on the drop zone.
空投区风太大
No jump tonight.
今晚不跳了!
The invasion has been postponed.
登陆行动已经延后
We're on a 24-hour stand-down.
现在进入24小时戒备状态!
Son of a bitch.
可恶!
Drill sergeants, take charge.
各排排长集合部队
Well, this is quite a surprise.
这真是出人意料之外
Not particularly.
倒不见得
It so happens I rather expected it.
既来之则安之
Well, I can't see how you people can pass up $80,000 for the Cause
我实在无法理解你们 怎能为了八万块钱就从军
For whose cause?
我可不是为钱从军的
If you're so interested in serving a cause...
如果是为了薪给
...why don't you join the Army?
为何不干脆加入陆军?
I think it's clearing up.
天气要放晴了
You think it's clearing up?
你觉得会变晴?
No.
不会
I think it's clearing up.
我想是要放晴了
How are your men?
你的弟兄准备得如何?
They'll be fine.
他们没问题的
5:00 in New York.
现在纽约是五点钟
4:00 in Chicago.
芝加哥是四点钟
Happy hour, huh?
快乐时光 对吧?
Yeah.
是的..
Happy hour.
快乐时光
A couple of drinks.
喝它几杯
Maybe an early dinner before the theater.
或许在看电影前提早吃晚餐
A civilized place for civilized men.
那是文明人享受文明的地方
Should've been born earlier, Nix.
真该早点出生的 尼克
What, and give up all this?
然后抛弃这一切?
We'll go to Chicago, I'll take you there.
我们会去芝加哥的 我带你去
Yeah.
是喔..
We'll see.
再说吧...
Actually, you know who's from there?
事实上 你知道谁是芝加哥人?
Who? Oh, him.
谁? 他喔
712 days of that son of a bitch and here we are.
忍受他712个日子 我们终于熬过来了
You people are at the position of attention.
你们所有人应该立正站好!
Private Perconte, have you been blousing your trousers over your boots like a paratrooper?
派康提二等兵 你是学伞兵把裤管塞进靴子里?
No, sir.
没有 长官!
Then explain the creases at the bottom.
那你的裤脚怎么有皱摺?
No excuse, sir.
长官 没有理由
Volunteering for the Parachute Infantry is one thing, Perconte...
志愿加入空降部队是一回事 派康提
...but you've got a long way to prove you belong here.
但是 要成为伞兵 你还早咧
Your weekend pass is revoked.
你的周末外出取消了
Name?
名字?
Luz, George.
乔治鲁兹
Dirt in the rear side aperture.
准星后方有灰尘
Pass revoked.
外出取消
When did you sew on these chevrons, Sergeant Lipton?
你何时把这些阶级绣上去的 李普中士?
Yesterday, sir.
昨天 长官
Long enough to notice this. Revoked.
线头太长 外出取消
Sir.
是 长官
Name?
名字?
Malarkey, Donald G.
唐诺·马拉其!
Malarkey
马拉其?
Malarkey's slang for bullshit, isn't it?
换成俗语就是狗屎的意思 是吧?
Yes, sir.
是 长官
Rust on the butt plate hinge spring, Private Bullshit.
枪托折轴弹簧生锈 二等兵狗屎
Revoked.
外出取消
Name?
名字?
Liebgott, Joseph D., sir.
乔瑟夫·李高特 长官
Rusty bayonet, Liebgott.
刺刀生锈 李高特
You want to kill Germans?
你想杀德国佬吗?
Yes, sir.
是 长官
Not with this.
不是靠这玩意儿
I wouldn't take this rusty piece of shit to war.
我不会带这块废铁上战场
And I will not take you to war in your condition.
你们这种表现 我也不会带你们上战场
Now, thanks to these men and their infractions...
由于你们这些人犯错
...every man in the company who had a weekend pass...
连上所有周末外出的人
...has lost it.
全部取消休假
Change into your PT gear, we're running Currahee.
换上你们的操练服 我们要去跑步
2nd Platoon, fall out.
第二排解散
We have two minutes.
你们有两分钟时间
Fall out!
解散!
I ain't going up that hill.
我可不想上那座山
Perconte, what are you thinking of blousing your pants?
派康提 你干嘛摺你的裤管?
Shut up, okay?
马丁 你闭嘴好吗?
He gigged everyone.
他挑每个人的毛病
You should know better.
那你就应该更小心
Don't give him no excuses.
不要给他任何借口
Excuses?
借口?
Why don't you come here, look at these trousers...
你过来看看我的裤子
...get down and tell me if there's a crease?
蹲下来仔细瞧 告诉我哪里有摺痕?
Let's go on the road in PT formation.
好了 我们出发了 成体能训练队形
Let's move, move, move!
动作快!
Perconte, let's go, Perconte.
派康提 出发了
Private White, why are you not in your PT gear?
二等兵怀特 你为什么未着操练服?
I asked you a question, Private.
我在问你问题 二等兵
Oh, Easy Company.
Ｅ连的弟兄们
While you're running, don't worry.
专心跑步别担心
We'll take your dames to the movies.
我们会帮你们带小妞去看电影
Yeah, good, they need some female company.
很好 他们需要些女伴
Where do we run?
我们在哪儿跑步?
Currahee.
葛拉锡 (新兵营)
What does "Currahee" mean?
那是什么意思?
We stand alone.
我们团结一致
How far up, how far down?
去跑多远? 回跑多远?
Three miles up, three miles down.
前去三里 回来三里
And what company is this?
我们叫做什么连?
Easy Company.
Ｅ连
- And what do we do? - Stand alone.
- 我们该做什么? - 团结一致!
Do not help that man! Do not help that man!
不准帮那个人!
We do not stop.
我们不停下
You've got 30 minutes to get to the top of this mountain...
你们要想在空降部队混
...if you want to serve in the Paratroopers.
就给我在30分钟内跑上山头
Hi-ho, Silver!
冲啊 骏马!
You can make it up there.
加油 你们跑得到的
Come on.
加油
Come on, Alley, let's go.
艾利 快跟上
Come on, Guarnere.
加油 葛奈瑞
Christenson, come on.
克里斯登生 加油
I never thought I'd see the day, Private Wynn.
我没想到你办的到 二等兵怀恩
We are coming on 23 minutes.
我们23分钟就跑到了
That may be good enough for the rest of the 506...
这或许对其他506团的部队来说够好了
...but that is not good enough for Easy Company.
但是对Ｅ连而言还不够
We can make it, we can do this, come on.
第二排 我们办得到的
I'm going to say something.
我有话要说
To who?
跟谁说?
Lieutenant Winters.
温特斯少尉
What is it?
什么事?
Permission to speak, sir?
请求发言 长官
Permission granted.
请求许可
Sir, we got nine companies, sir.
长官 我们一共有9个连
That we do.
没错
How come we're the only company...
为何我们是唯一每周五晚上
...marching every Friday night, 12 miles, full pack in the pitch dark?
都要全副武装摸黑跑12里的一连?
Why do you think, Private Randleman?
那你以为是为什么呢? 二等兵蓝道曼?
Lieutenant Sobel hates us, sir.
索柏中尉恨我们
Lieutenant Sobel does not hate Easy Company, Private Randleman.
索柏中尉并不恨Ｅ连 二等兵蓝道曼
He just hates you.
他只恨你一个人
Thank you, sir.
谢谢你 长官
He hates him back.
他也恨他
He hates you, too, Muck.
他也恨你呢 穆克
Lieutenant Winters, I want canteens out of belts with the caps unscrewed.
温特斯少尉 所有水壶都卸下腰带 盖子打开
Easy Company, canteens out and open.
全Ｅ连都要卸水壶 把盖子打开
On my command, they will pour the contents onto the ground.
听我命令 所有人把水壶里的水倒在地上
On the CO's order, you will upend your canteen.
听指挥官口令 把水壶倒过来
Now, Lieutenant.
就是现在 少尉
Pour them.
倒
Who is this?
这是谁?
Christenson.
克里斯登生
Why is there no water in your canteen?
你水壶里为何没水?
You drank from your canteen, didn't you?
你喝了水 是吧?
Lieutenant Winters.
温特斯少尉!
Yes, sir.
长官!
Was this man ordered to not drink from his canteen during the Friday night march?
是不是有规定 不准在周五夜跑喝水?
He was, sir.
是的 长官!
Private Christenson, you have disobeyed a direct order.
二等兵克里斯登生 你违反命令
You will fill your canteen...
把水壶给我装满
...and repeat all 12 miles of the march immediately.
再去跑上12里
Yes, sir.
是 长官
Fall out!
离开!
What in the name of God are you doing with my company?
你是怎么带我的连?
You're late and you allow troopers to disobey direct orders?
你不但迟到 还允许士兵违反命令
No excuse, sir.
没有理由 长官
You're making me look bad, Lieutenant.
你让我很难看 少尉!
This is not Dog Company. This is not Fox Company.
我们不是Ｄ连也不是Ｆ连
This is Easy Company.
这是Ｅ连
Under my command, this will be the first...
在我领导之下 我们将是第一
...and finest company in this regiment.
也是军团里最好的连
I want the names of six men.
我要你找出六个人
Their infractions and your disciplinary recommendations on my desk by 0130.
把他们的名字 犯的错误 以及你的教化建言 在1点30分前放在我桌上
Is that clear?
听清楚了吗?
What infractions, sir?
什么样的错误 长官?
Find some.
你去找出来
So, what'd you do?
结果你怎么做?
Picked six men and gave them latrine duty.
我找了六个人去扫军厕
The lucky six?
哪六个倒霉鬼?
McDowell, Toye, Perconte.
麦唐纳 托依 派康提
Lipton, Muck and Guarnere.
李普 穆克及葛奈瑞
Why them?
为何找他们?
It was their turn.
本来就轮到他们扫
Sobel's a genius.
索柏真是个天才
I had a headmaster just like him in prep school.
我在预校就有个教官像他
I know the type.
他这种人我很了解
Lewis.
路易斯
Michelangelo's a genius, Beethoven's a genius.
米开朗基罗才是天才 贝多芬也是天才
You know a man in this company who wouldn't double-time Currahee with a full pack...
你知道本连有谁不愿意全付武装跑酷拉练
...just to piss in that guy's morning coffee?
然后在那个傢伙的早餐咖啡里撒尿?
Let's go, let's go.
赶快 赶快
Stand in the door.
- 站到门边 - 跳
1,000, 2,000.
一秒 两秒
You just broke both your legs, Private Gordon.
二等兵戈登 你刚跌断你的双腿
Are you trying to get killed?
你想要自杀吗?
No, sir.
不想 长官
Stand in the door.
站到门边
Shit.
可恶
To the wall.
跑到墙边
Over as a team.
大家一起过去
Go on, against the wall.
去 靠着墙边
Jesus, what the hell is this?
老天 这是什么玩意儿?
That's pig guts, boy.
那是猪
Goddamn it!
可恶!
Why are you here, Private Gordon?
二等兵戈登 你为何来这里?
To be in the Airborne, sir.
我想成为伞兵 长官
I don't believe you. Why are you here, Private Gordon?
我不相信 二等兵戈登 你为何来这里?
You have 50 minutes to the top and back, and I will be watching you.
给你50分钟跑到山头再回来 我会盯着你
What are you waiting for?
你还在等什么?
Easy Company has the finest performance record in the entire 2nd Battalion.
Ｅ连在第二营表现最好
I believe every bit of that is thanks to you.
我相信这全都归功于你
Congratulations, Captain Sobel.
恭喜你 索柏上尉
Thank you, sir.
谢谢你 长官
Isn't that Lieutenant Winters leading Easy Company in PT?
正在带穿操练服的Ｅ连操练的 是不是温斯特少尉?
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
He's a damned good man.
他真是好军人
I was planning on giving him a set of these today.
我今天本要颁发他一副这个
Why don't you do it? He'd be proud to get them from you.
由你来好了 他一定会觉得很荣幸
Pornography, contraband.
色情书刊 违禁品
Non-regulation clothing, contraband.
规定外的衣服 违禁品
This man had 200 prophylactic kits in his footlocker.
这人柜子里有200个保险套
How in the name of God was he going to have the strength to fight the war?
他哪里还有力气打仗?
How is it Private Tipper...
二等兵提波那里来那么多
...has spare time for so much correspondence?
空闲时间看那么多的信?
Captain, are personal letters to be considered contraband?
连长! 私人信件也算违禁品?
These men aren't paratroopers yet, Lieutenant.
这些人还不是伞兵 少尉
They have no personal property.
他们没有私人物品
What is this?
这是什么?
Anybody?
谁愿意回答?
It's a can of peaches, sir.
那是罐桃子 长官
Lieutenant Nixon thinks this is a can of peaches.
尼克森少尉认为这是罐桃子
That is incorrect, Lieutenant.
这是不正确的 少尉
Your weekend pass is cancelled.
你的周末外出取消了
This is United States Army property...
这是美国陆军财产
...which was taken, without authorization, from my mess facility...
是从我们伙房未经允许带出的
...and I will not tolerate thievery in my unit.
而我绝不容忍连上有任何偷窃物品
Whose footlocker is this?
这是谁的置物柜?
Private Parks, sir.
二等兵帕克斯的 长官
Get rid of him.
把他退训
All weekend passes are cancelled.
所有周末外出许可取消
Officers included.
包括军官的
Carry on.
继续动作
Lieutenant Winters.
温特斯少尉
Colonel Sink has seen fit to promote you.
辛克上校觉得你可以晋升了
As First Lieutenant, you'll serve as my executive officer.
身为中尉 你将担任我的值星官
Congratulations.
恭喜
Thank you, sir.
谢谢你 长官
And, as a test of your organizational skills and command potential...
还有 为了训练你的组织能力和领导潜力
...I am designating you mess officer for 14 days.
我现在指派你担任14天的伙房官
Report to the mess kitchen at 0515 hours.
5点15到厨房报道
Company breakfast to be served at 0600.
连上早餐6点开饭
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
And, Dick, there's rain forecast tomorrow...
还有 迪克 气象报告说明天会下雨
...so the company will have a light afternoon of lecture and classroom instruction.
所以明天下午连上在室内上些轻松的课
I think a special meal before their afternoon off...
我想在下午休息前来个特别点心
...would be a welcome change of pace.
那会是改变步调的好开始
Would you agree?
你同意吗?
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
I like spaghetti.
我喜欢意大利面
Hold on, more coming.
等等 马上再来
These guys are packing it away.
这些家伙还想打包呢
This stuff is orange.
这玩意儿是桔色的
Spaghetti ain't supposed to be orange.
意大利面不应该是桔色的
This ain't spaghetti.
这不是意大利面
This is army noodles with ketchup.
这是沾了番茄酱的陆军面条
You ain't got to eat it.
又没规定你一定得吃
Oh, come on, Gonorrhea, as a fellow Italian...
拜托 淋病先生 身为意大利人
...you know that calling this spaghetti is a mortal sin.
称这垃圾为意大利面会良心不安的
- I'll have it. - No, I'm eating here.
- 你不要我要 - 不 我在吃
Hey, get out of here.
闪一边去
Orders changed, get up!
命令更改 起立!
Lectures are cancelled.
室内课程取消
Easy Company is running up Currahee.
Ｅ连现在改在营区跑步
Move, move!
动作快!
Three miles up, three miles down.
去三里 回三里
Hi-ho, Silver!
冲啊 骏马!
Let's go, let's go.
出发了
You're a washout, Private Hoobler!
你是个懦夫 二等兵胡伯勒
You should pack up both your ears and go home.
你应该把耳朵都打包好回家
Looks like Gordon's done.
看来戈登已经不行了
Aren't you, Gordon. You finished?
是不是啊 戈登? 你玩完了吗?
You do not deserve to get your wings.
你不配得到你的伞兵勋章
Private Randleman, you look tired.
一等兵蓝道曼 你看来很疲倦
There's an ambulance waiting for you at the bottom of the hill.
山脚有辆救护车在等着你
It can all be over right now.
你现在就可以解脱
No more pain, no more Currahee.
再也没有痛苦 再也没有新兵训练
No more Captain Sobel.
再也没有索柏上尉
"We pull upon the risers We fall upon the grass
∮我们拉着扬升缆 降落在草地∮
"We never land upon our feet We always hit our ass
∮我们不用脚落地 永远臀落地∮
"Hide tidee, Christ almighty Who the hell are we?
∮万能之神 我们是何人? ∮
"Zim zam, goddamn! We're Airborne Infantry
∮我们是天杀的伞兵∮
"We pull upon the risers We fall upon the grass
∮我们拉着扬升缆 降落在草地∮
"We never land upon our feet We always hit our ass
∮我们不用脚落地 永远臀落地∮
"Hide tidee, Christ almighty Who the hell are we?
∮万能之神 我们是何人? ∮
"Zim zam, goddamn! We're Airborne Infantry"
∮我们是天杀的伞兵∮
So, do we feel like we're ready to be army paratroopers?
你们觉得准备好成为陆军伞兵了吗?
Yes, Sergeant.
是的 中士
I hope so.
我也希望如此
This'll be the first of five exits from a C-47 aircraft scheduled for today.
这是我们今天预定从C47上跳五次的第一趟
Get ready!
准备
Stand up!
起立
Hook up!
挂钩
Upon successful completion of your fifth and final jump...
一旦你跳完五次 也是最后一跳
...you'll be certified army paratroopers.
你就成为合格的伞兵
Check equipment!
检查装备!
Sound off for equipment check!
报告检查装备
Nine okay.
9号就绪
Eight okay.
8号就绪
Seven okay.
7号就绪
Six okay.
6号就绪
Five okay.
5号就绪
Four okay.
4号就绪
Three okay.
3号就绪
Two okay.
2号就绪
One okay.
1号就绪
There'll be a lot of men dropping from the sky today.
今天会有许多人从天而降
Hopefully, under deployed canopies.
希望大家的伞都能开
Stand in the door!
站到门口
I guarantee you're going to love it, Lieutenant.
我保证你会喜欢的 中尉
Go, go!
跳!
Jumping from 1,000 feet AGL...
我们从实际高度一千尺跳
...in sticks of 12 jumpers per aircraft.
一架飞机一梯次跳12个人
All you have to do is remember what you were taught...
你们只要牢记所学的
...and I guarantee you, gravity will take care of the rest.
我保证剩下的就让地心引力去完成了
Go, go, go, go!
跳!
Damn it.
可恶
And, gentlemen, rest assured...
各位 还有最重要的...
...any refusals in the aircraft or at the door...
任何在机舱里或是门边拒跳的人
...and I guarantee you, you will be out of the Airborne.
我保证你会被踢出空降部队
Four okay.
4号就绪
Three okay.
3号就绪
Two okay.
2号就绪
One okay.
1号就绪
Stand in the door.
站到门口
Go!
跳!
1,000, 2,000, 3,000, 4,000, 5,000, 6,000...
一秒 两秒 三秒 四秒 五秒 六秒
...7,000, 8,000, 9,000!
七秒 八秒 九秒!
Hi-ho, Silver!
冲啊 骏马
Now just think, if you had any class or style like me...
你想想 如果你像我一样帅
...somebody might mistake you for somebody.
别人可能以为你是个大人物
You mean like your fucking sergeant?
你是说像个班长?
I'm just kidding.
开玩笑而已
Congratulations, Martin.
恭喜你 马丁
Corporal Toye, there will be no leaning in my company.
托依下士! 在我连里是不容许任何偏差的
Are those dusty jump wings?
这是沾了灰尘的伞兵徽吗?
How do you expect to slay the Huns with dust on your jump wings?
伞兵徽要是沾上灰 怎能用来杀德国佬呢?
Luz, just give me a drink.
鲁兹 给我杯酒就是了
Hell of an idea, Joe.
当然
There you go.
拿去
Three miles up, three miles down.
去三里 回三里
Ten-hut!
立正!
Well, at ease, paratroopers.
伞兵们 请稍息
Good evening, Easy Company.
Ｅ连的弟兄大家晚安
Evening, sir.
晚安 长官
Now, Parachute Infantry is a brand-new concept...
伞兵部队在美国军队史上
...in American military history.
是个崭新的概念
But, by God, the 506 is going to forge that brand-new concept...
但506团绝对有能力将这新观念
...into victory.
转化为胜利
Yes, sir.
是的 长官!
I want you to know that I'm damned proud of each and every one of you.
我要你们知道我是多么的以你们为荣
Now, you deserve this party.
这场宴会是你们应得的
Thank you, Sergeant Grant.
谢谢你 葛兰特中士
Sir.
长官
So, I want you to have fun and remember our motto:
现在我要你们尽情享受 并牢记我们的座右铭:
Currahee!
团结一致!
Petty.
派提!
Map.
拿地图来
Come on.
快点!
Ah, Christ.
老天
We're in the wrong position.
我们的位置不对
We're textbook position for ambush, sir.
长官 我们处于教范中伏击的位置
We should sit tight, let the enemy team come into our killing zone.
我们应该静候 让敌人进入我们的猎杀范围
They're right out there somewhere.
他们就在附近
Let's just get them.
我们去消灭他们吧
Sir, we have perfect cover here.
长官 这里有绝佳的屏障
Lieutenant, deploy your troops.
中尉 部署你的弟兄
2nd Platoon, move out.
第二排! 前进!
What?
什么?
Tactical column.
成战术纵队
Captain, you've just been killed, along with 95 percent of your company.
连长 你刚跟连上95%的士兵都阵亡了
Your outfit?
你们的番号?
Easy Company, 2nd Battalion, 506th.
506团 第二营 Ｅ连
Leave three wounded men on the ground and report back to the assembly area.
留下三个受伤士兵 然后向集结区报道
Goddamn it.
可恶..
You, you, you.
你 你 你
Well, what are you going to do?
你要怎么办?
Nothing, just keep training the men.
不怎么办 继续训练他们
Am I interrupting?
我打搅你们了?
No, no.
没有
Lieutenant Lewis Nixon.
路易斯尼克森中尉
Lieutenant Harry Welsh, just in from the 82nd.
这是刚从82师调来的哈利威尔旭中尉
Congratulations on the promotion.
恭喜你荣升了
Thanks, if you want to call it that.
谢谢 如果那算是晋升
You'll learn him pretty quickly.
你很快就会发现他是个
No flaws, no vices, no sense of humor.
没缺点 没怪癖 没有幽默感的人
Just like your chums up at battalion staff.
就像你在营部的朋友一样
What's up?
什么事?
I'm hearing a lot of rumblings.
我听到许多是非
Sobel?
关于索柏?
Just talking about that.
我们正在谈这事
So, he gets a little jumpy in the field?
他在野战场上有些神经质?
He gets jumpy and then you get killed.
对 他一神经你就阵亡
That's nice.
那真好
Yeah, listen, if we discuss it, I think it should just be amongst ourselves.
是啊 听好了 如果要讨论 仅限于内部
Absolutely.
那当然
2nd Platoon, ready?
第二排准备好了吗?
Ready, sir.
准备好了 长官
Then get them in formation.
那就叫他们整队
We're moving out.
我们要出发了
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
Shut up, Cobb.
卡伯 闭嘴
You got to admit it.
你应该承认的
He's got no chance.
他没有机会的
Either the Krauts will get him or one of us.
他若非被德军做掉 就是自己人动手
Who, Sobel?
说谁? 索柏吗?
He screwed up one maneuver.
他搞砸了一个演习
Well, you know, I'm always fumbling with grenades.
你知道我常把玩手榴弹
It would be easy if one went off by accident, you know?
要是不小心炸掉一枚是很容易的事
Well, now they must have put him in charge for a reason.
他们让他负责指挥一定有原因
Yeah, 'cause the Army wouldn't make a mistake, right?
因为陆军从不犯错 是吗 西福弟
Going my way?
跟我一起走吗?
Wherever the train takes me.
火车去哪我就去哪
Where do you suppose that might be?
那会是哪里?
I haven't got a clue
我不知道
Yeah, come on, take a guess.
来吧 猜猜看
Atlantic, Pacific, Atlantic?
大西洋? 太平洋? 大西洋?
I'm not the intelligence officer.
我又不是情报局的军官
Well, as such, I, of course, know, but if I told you, I'd have to kill you.
我是知道要去哪 但我告诉你就得杀了你
So, don't tell me.
那就别告诉我
New York City.
先到纽约
Troopship.
上兵船
England.
再到英国
We're invading Europe, my friend.
我们要登陆欧洲 兄弟
Fortress Europa.
攻击欧罗巴壁垒
Since when do I drink?
我何时开始喝酒了?
If I thought you'd drink it, I wouldn't offer it to you.
我如果知道你喝酒 才不会请你喝
Nix?
尼克?
What are you going to do when you get into combat?
你从战场上回来后会干什么?
I have every confidence in my scrounging abilities.
我行骗取巧样样行
And I have a case of VAT 69 hidden in your footlocker.
而且你柜子里还藏有一箱陈年威士忌呢
Really?
真的吗?
Oh, yeah.
当然
'Morning.
早安
This could turn into a real nice trip.
这将会是趟美好旅程
"Dear sir or madam:
亲爱的先生女士
"Soon your son will drop from the sky to engage and defeat the enemy.
你们的儿子很快就要从天而降 跟敌人作战并击败他们
"Your frequent letters of love and encouragement...
你们爱与鼓励的信
"...will arm him with a fighting heart.
将可武装他战斗的心
"With that he cannot fail, but will win glory for himself...
借着它 他不会失败而会为自己赢得荣耀
"...make you proud of him, and his country ever grateful...
让你们以他为荣 而国家也感谢他
"...for his service in its hour of need.
在国家需要的时候 挺身而出
"Signed, Herbert M. Sobel, Captain Commanding."
署名: 贺博索柏 上尉连长
Right now, some lucky bastard's headed for the South Pacific.
就在此刻 已经有许多走狗屎运的人 朝着南太平洋出发
Oh, what I'd give.
好想跟他们换
He's going to get billeted on some tropical island.
被分配到某热带小岛
Keep talking.
继续说
Sitting under a palm tree with six naked native girls...
跟当地的六个裸体的女孩坐在棕榈树下
...helping him cut up coconuts so he can hand-feed them to the flamingos.
她们帮他剥椰子 所以他可以用手来喂火烈鸟
Flamingos are mean.
火烈鸟很凶
They bite.
会咬人的
So do the naked native girls.
裸女也会的
With any luck.
如果运气好
Hey, guys, I'm glad I'm going to Europe.
大伙们 我很高兴要去欧洲
Hitler gets one of these right across the windpipe.
我在希特勒喉管上割一刀
Roosevelt changes Thanksgiving to Joe Toye Day...
罗斯福会把感恩节改成乔托依纪念日
...and pays me $10,000 a year for the rest of my fucking life.
还要终生每年付我一万元
What if we don't get to Europe?
如果我们不是去欧洲呢?
What if they send us to North Africa?
如果他们送我们去北非呢?
My brother's in North Africa.
我老哥就在北非
He says it's hot.
他说那里很热
Really, it's hot in Africa?
真的? 非洲很热?
Shut up.
闭嘴!
The point is, it don't matter where we go.
重点是无论我们去哪里
In combat, the only person you can trust...
一旦我们进入战斗 你唯一可信任的
...is yourself and the fellow next to you.
就是你自己和身旁的人
Hey, as long as he's a paratrooper.
只要他是个伞兵
Oh, yeah?
是吗?
And what if that paratrooper turns out to be Sobel?
万一那个伞兵是索柏?
If I'm next to Sobel in combat, I'm moving on down the line.
若作战时我旁边是索柏 我会移动战线
Hook up with some other officer, like Heyliger or Winters.
去找其他的军官 像是海立格或是温特斯
I like Winters, he's a good man.
我喜欢温特斯 他是个好人
But when the bullets start flying...
可是当子弹开始飞舞时
...I don't know if I want a Quaker doing my fighting for me.
我不知道我是不是要让个贵格教徒为我作战
How do you know he's a Quaker?
你怎么知道他是贵格教徒?
He ain't Catholic.
他绝不是天主教徒
Neither is Sobel.
索柏也不是
That prick's a son of Abraham.
他是个犹太佬
He's what?
他是什么?
He's a Jew.
他是犹太人
I'm a Jew.
我也是犹太人
Congratulations.
恭喜你
Get your nose out of my face.
快从我面前消失
What's all that about?
那是怎么回事?
Gonorrhea called Sobel a Jew.
淋病先生说索柏是犹太人
Liebgott took offense 'cause he's a Jew too.
李高特跟他冲起来 因为他自己也是犹太人
Fighting over Sobel, that's smart.
为了索柏打架 真是聪明
Attack!
攻击!
No, you want to kill him!
不对 你要有杀气
Parry right, parry left.
防右刺 防左刺
Thrust!
原地突刺!
Take cover.
还原
Okay.
好了
Yesterday, we talked about magnetic declination...
昨天我们谈到了磁场偏移
...and the "left add, right subtract" rule.
以及左加右减定律
Today we're putting it into practice.
今天我们将实地操作
There are two basic types of fighting positions.
作战有两种基本位置
The first is the prepared position.
第一种是守备位置
The advantages of a prepared position are that it gives you cover and concealment.
守备位置的优点是它提供你掩护及隐蔽
Commence fire!
开始射击!
We'll then maneuver right in through these trees.
然后我们都将朝这树林移动
At the same time, our second platoon, in this particular case, moves over here.
同时 在这个例子下 第二排将移动到这里
He's then going to close with and kill or capture that German.
他接着将封锁消灭或俘虏德军
Sobel's late.
索柏迟了
Why is there a fence here?
这里为什么会有围篱?
There should be no fence here.
这里不应该有围篱
- Tibbo - Yes, sir
- 提波! - 是的 长官!
Give me the map.
地图给我
Perconte, Luz.
派康提 鲁兹 集合弟兄
Get the men, get them...
叫他们...
Take cover behind those trees.
在树后找掩护
You heard the word. Let's go over there.
都听到了 动作快
There should be no... There should be no fence here.
这里不应该有围篱
We could go over it, sir.
我们可以跨越它 长官
Really?
真的吗?
That's not the point. Where the goddamn...
这不是重点 我们到底...
Where the goddamn hell are we?
在什么鬼地方?
- Perconte? - Yeah.
- 派康提? - 干嘛?
- Sobel's lost again, right? - Yeah, he's lost.
- 索柏又迷路了 对不对? - 是啊 他迷路了
Fucking Christ.
真该死
Can you do Major Horton?
你会模仿贺顿少校吗?
Does a wild bear crap in the woods, son?
- 小子 有人脱裤子放屁的吗? - 安静
Maybe the good major can goose this schmuck.
或许这位好少校能耍耍这笨蛋
Get us moving?
让我们继续前进吧?
No way.
不 门儿都没有
Yes. You got to.
要 你一定要
All right, just this once.
好啦 下不为例
Three-five-six-eight-three-three.
三...五...六...八...三...三
Isn't that the intersection?
这不就是交会点吗?
No, sir, it's here.
不 长官 是在这里
You're a full grid off.
你偏离整个坐标格了
Goddamn it.
可恶
Is there a problem, Captain Sobel?
索柏上尉 有什么问题吗?
Who said that?
谁在说话?
Who broke silence?
是谁违反通话静默?
I think it's Major Horton, sir.
我想那是贺顿少校 长官
Major Horton?
贺顿少校?
What is he... Did he join us?
他怎么...他也参加演习了吗?
I think maybe he's moving between the platoons, sir.
我想也许他是在各排间游走 长官
What is the goddamn holdup, Mr. Sobel?
索柏先生 你停止不动 是在搞什么鬼?
A fence, sir.
有座篱笆 长官
God!
我的天
A barbed wire fence.
有座铁刺围篱
Oh, that dog just ain't going to hunt!
那只狗就是不会打猎
Now, you cut that fence and get this goddamn platoon on the move!
你现在把铁网剪了 叫你的排继续前进
Yes, sir!
是 长官!
Where are my goddamn wire cutters?
我那该死的剪线器在哪里?
We have to move.
我们必须前进
Sir, without Captain Sobel and 1st Platoon?
长官 不等索柏连长跟第一排了吗?
It's a T-intersection. We improvise.
这是个"T"字形交汇点 我们自行发挥
Double envelopment laid on a base of fire to cut the road in all directions.
以火力掩护双重的包围 封锁道路四方
Hook right with first squad. Tell Guarnere to move left with second.
向右与第一班会合 叫葛奈瑞和第二班向左移动
I'll be right up the middle with third, go.
我会和第三班从中线突破
Yes, sir.
是的 长官!
Deary me.
我的天
Bloody hell.
搞什么鬼
You've done it now, Yanks.
你成功了 美国佬
You've captured me.
你抓到我了
Hi-ho, Silver!
冲啊~ 骏马!
Would that be the enemy?
那是你们的敌人吗?
As a matter of fact, yes.
事实上 是的
Good work, 2nd Platoon.
干得好 第二排
We took the objective.
我们攻占目标了
Who is the idiot who cut that man's fence?
哪个白痴把那个人的篱笆给剪了?
I was ordered to, sir.
有人命令我剪的 长官
By whom?
是谁?
Major Horton, sir.
贺顿少校 长官
Major Horton?
贺顿少校?
Yes, sir.
是的 长官!
Major Horton told you to do that?
贺顿少校叫你这么做?
Major Horton ordered you to cut the fence?
贺顿少校命令你把围篱剪了?
Yes, he did.
是的 他说的
Major Horton is on leave in London.
贺顿少校正在伦敦休假
Get those cows out of here.
把那些牛赶走
Lieutenant Winters.
温特斯中尉
With Captain Sobel's compliments, sir.
我带来了索柏上尉的"嘉勉" 长官
Lieutenant.
中尉
Oh, for crying out loud.
我的天啊
This spells court-martial.
我看要军法审判了
Wide open! Yes.
空位投篮!进了
No, sir, I do not understand.
不是的 长官 我不明白
Your orders to me were to inspect the latrines at 1000 hours.
你的命令是要我在10点时检查厕所
From 0930 to 0955 I was censoring the enlisted men's mail by order of Colonel Strayer.
从9点30到9点55 我奉史崔尔上校的命令查阅士兵们的信件
At 1000 hours I followed your orders to the minute.
10点整 我分秒不差执行了你的命令
I changed that time to 0945.
我把时间改到9点45了
No one told me, sir.
没人告诉我 长官
I telephoned.
我打过电话
I'm quartered with a family that has no telephone.
我的排上没有电话
And sent a runner.
我还派了传令兵
No runner found me, Captain.
传令兵没有找到我 上尉
Irregardless, when given a task to perform by a ranking officer
不管那么多 当上属长官指派任务时
you should have delegated your task of latrine inspection to another officer.
你应将检查厕所的工作 移交给其他军官
You failed to do so.
你并未这样做
Were I to let such a failure of duty by my own X O go unpunished...
难道要我不处罚犯错的值星官
...what kind of message is that to the men?
那样士兵们会怎样想?
I performed my duty as I was ordered, sir.
我照命令执行了任务 长官
And I disagree.
但我不认为
So, your options are quite simple, Lieutenant.
所以你现在的选择很简单 中尉
Punishment for your offenses will be denial of a 48-hour pass for 60 days.
对你错误的处罚 将是60天内48小时不许外出
Stand before me at attention.
在我面前立正站好
Or you may initiate a letter of appeal and request a trial by court-martial.
或者你可以上诉 并要求召开军事法庭
You spend your weekends on the base anyway, Dick.
反正你周末休假都待在营区 迪克
Be a man, take the punishment.
像个男子汉接受处罚吧
May I borrow your pen, sir?
能跟你借个笔吗 长官?
My endorsement, sir.
我的签署 长官
I request trial by court-martial.
我要求开军事法庭
We lost Winters to battalion mess.
温特斯被调去营部伙房了
You're shitting me.
你在开玩笑吧?
No.
真的!
Strayer did it, while they try to figure out the procedures for his court-martial.
史崔尔调的 为了让他们能想出军法审判他的程序
Nix better find a loophole and get him out.
那尼克最好挖个洞把他救援出来
And if he don't?
万一他不出来呢?
Winters scrambles eggs while the rest of us make the big jump with Sobel.
我们和索柏大空降的时候 温特斯却在炒蛋
Not me.
别叫我去
So we're going through with this, right?
所以我们决定这么做了?
We've got to do something.
我们总得做点什么
Yeah.
好
All right.
好吧..
Good.
好吧...
But we'd all better be clear on the consequences.
我们最好都清楚要承担的后果
- I don't care about the consequences. - You got.
- 我才不在乎后果 - 要在乎
We could be lined up against a wall and shot.
我们可能排排站被枪毙
Now, I'm ready to face that.
我已经做好这样的准备
And every one of us had better be, too.
大家最好也都准备好
I will not follow that man into combat.
我不会跟随那个人作战
Me neither.
我也不会
All right.
很好
Then let's do it.
我们就这么做
"I hereby...
我在此声明
"...no longer wish to serve...
不愿再担任
"...as a non-commissioned officer...
士官
"...in Easy Company."
管理Ｅ连
All right, boys.
很好 诸位
Good luck.
祝好运!
I ought to have you all shot!
我应把你们都枪毙
This is nothing less than an act of mutiny...
在我们准备反攻欧洲的时候
...while we prepare for the goddamn invasion of Europe.
这跟军事叛乱没有两样
Sergeant Harris.
哈理士中士
Sir.
是的 长官
Turn in your stripes, collect your gear.
缴交军徽 收拾装备
You are hereby transferred out of my regiment.
我要调你离开我的团
Sir.
是的 长官
Get out.
离开
Sergeant Ranney.
蓝尼中士
Sir.
长官
You consider yourself lucky, I'm only busting you to private.
算你走运 我只把你降为二等兵
All of you NCOs have disgraced the 101st Airborne.
你们这些士官已经让101空降师蒙羞
Consider yourself lucky that we are on the eve of the largest action in the history of warfare...
因为我们正在历史上最大战役的前夕
...which leaves me no choice but to spare your lives.
我只好饶了你们的性命
Now, get out of my office and get out of my sight.
离开我的办公室 别让我看到你们
Get.
离开
Keep them coming, atta-boy.
继续搬给我 很好 就是这样
I can only speculate, sir. Most of the men would never do this...
我只能这样猜想 长官 大部分人不会这么做
...but I believe just a few of the sergeants may have felt...
但有少部分的士官
...their loyalty lay more to the platoon than to the company.
觉得对排上的忠诚高于对连上
And these few sergeants convinced all of the other NCOs in your company...
而这些少数军官说服连上其他士官
...to turn in their stripes?
将他们的军阶交出?
As staff sergeants, they have a great amount of influence, sir.
作为幕僚士官 他们影响力很大 长官
But as I say, the rest are good men.
可是就像我说的 其他的都是好人
I know them, I can work with them.
我了解他们 我可以和他们共事
This business with the Winters' court-martial...
关于将温斯特交付军法一事
...has been an unpleasant distraction.
已经造成不愉快的骚动
Indeed it has, sir.
的确 的确是这样的 长官
However...
总之
...your command of Easy Company has been exemplary.
你对Ｅ连的领导一直可为模范
Thank you, sir.
谢谢你 长官
In fact, except for the actions of a few of your non-coms...
事实上 除了这些少数士官的行为外
...I believe you've fielded one of the finest companies of soldiers I've ever seen.
我相信你所统领的是我所见过最好的连队
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
Herbert, Division has established...
贺博! 师部
...a parachute training school at Chilton Foliat.
已经在奇顿佛列建了一所伞兵训练学校
The idea is for non-infantry types who...
目的是让在即将展开的登陆中
...were vital to the coming invasion...
非步兵的重要人员
...such as doctors and chaplains, to take jump training there.
如医生及牧师参加跳伞训练
I can't think of anyone more qualified...
坦白说 除你之外我想不出
...to command such a school than you are.
更适合去该校指导的人
Sir?
长官?
I'm reassigning you to Chilton Foliat.
我将你转调到奇顿佛列
I'm losing Easy Company?
我要离开Ｅ连?
The war effort needs you elsewhere.
战争需要你去别的地方
Permission to speak, sir?
请求发言 长官
Granted.
请求许可
Is... Who will be replacing me?
谁会来替代我?
Lieutenant Meehan from Baker Company is senior.
Ｂ连的米汉中尉比较资深
Good luck at Chilton Foliat, Herbert.
祝你在奇顿佛列好运 贺博
Don't let us down now.
别让我们失望了
No, sir.
我不会的 长官
Carry on.
继续工作
2nd Platoon, listen up.
第二排听好
I want the first squad and A-side tents right up there.
我要一班在这边搭帐篷
Third squad, second row...
第三班 到第二列
Holy shit.
我的老天
No, it's all right. We're tommies...
没关系的 老兄 我们是英军
...not bleeding boche.
不是死德军
Is all this real?
这是真的吗?
Yeah, yeah.
是啊
Some is from the Hermans, somebody's tailor's knocked up.
有些是从赫曼裁缝店赶工缝制
For you, so you can get your mince pies on this Jerry clobber...
用来给你们用馅饼砸德国佬的
...if you know what I mean.
如果你懂我的意思
Not really.
不太懂
Mack, you got a Luger?
老兄 有鲁格枪(德军手枪)?
I'm dying to get a real Luger.
我好想摸摸真的鲁格枪
Yeah, go on then.
有啊 拿去
A quick butchers, yeah?
真是把好枪 对不?
Boy, she sure is a doozy.
乖乖 她真是棒极了
Yeah, it's pukka, ain't it?
她真是高级 对不?
What?
什么?
Hey, Petty.
派提!
Hey, mate.
老兄
You're having a bath if you think you're half-inching that.
你可别得寸进尺
Oh, yeah.
哦 对
Sorry. Well, good luck.
抱歉! 祝你好运!
You too, mate.
你也是 老兄
What's up, Hoobs?
什么事 胡伯?
These men have been through the toughest training the Army has to offer.
这些人经历了陆军最严格的训练
Under the worst possible circumstances.
在极艰困的环境下
And they volunteered for it.
而且这些人都是自愿从军
Christ, I was just shooting craps with them. It's not like...
拜托 迪克 我不过是跟他们掷骰子 又不是...
You know why they volunteered?
你知道他们为什么自愿吗?
So, when things got really bad, the man next to them would be the best.
情况变得很糟时 壕沟中身旁的都将是上上之才
Not some draftee who's going to get him killed.
而不是会害死他们的充数兵
Are you ticked because they like me?
难道你因为他们喜欢我而不高兴?
Because I'm spending time to get to know my soldiers?
因为我花时间去了解我的弟兄?
You've been with these guys for what, two years?
拜托 你和他们相处两年了吧?
I've been here for six days.
我才来这里六天
You're gambling, Bob.
你是在赌博 鲍伯
So what? Soldiers do that.
那又怎样? 阿兵哥都赌博
I don't deserve a reprimand for it.
这不值得你训我
What if you'd won?
如果你赢了呢?
What?
什么?
Never put yourself in a position where you can take from these men.
千万不要给自己有任何占士兵便宜的机会
Lieutenant Meehan?
米汉中尉?
Enter.
进来
On the last training jump, I had a compass.
在上次的跳伞练习 我带着罗盘
Close the flap.
把帐帘放下
Then we turn left.
然后我们向左转
Yeah.
对
Bearing zero-four-two.
航线042度
12 minutes.
飞12分钟
Then another left?
然后再左转?
- Yes - Yeah
- 对! - 对!
Call it three-five-eight...
算是258度吧
...for 10 and a half minutes.
飞了十分半钟
Green light, right over Ramsbury.
绿灯亮起 正在兰姆斯柏瑞上方
Ramsbury.
兰姆斯柏瑞
Every single time.
每次都是一样
Linear distance on the grid of about...
用你图上的格数计算是从...
Okay.
嗯
Ramsbury.
兰姆斯柏瑞
Upottery.
尤波泰瑞
So...
所以...
It's Normandy.
这是诺曼底
St. Marie du Mont.
圣梅莉山岭
Causeway Number One.
一号堤道
Causeway Number Two.
二号堤道
The ultimate field problem.
最大的战地问题
The estuary of the Douve River divides two beachheads...
多佛河口分成两个滩头
...code-named Utah, here, and Omaha, here.
代号是犹他 这里 还有是奥马哈 这里
Seaborne Infantry will hit these beaches in force...
海运步兵大批抵达这些滩头...
...at a date and time to be specified.
...有待指定日期与时刻
H-hour, D-day.
代号H时 D日
Airborne's objective, gentlemen, is to take the town of Carentan...
空降部队的目标是拿下卡汉坦或叫卡云坦
...thus linking Utah and Omaha into a single, continuous beachhead.
借以将犹他及奥马哈连成一线
...linking Omaha and Utah into one continuous beachhead.
...借以将犹他及奥马哈连成一线
Each trooper will learn this operation by heart...
每位伞兵心里都要将任务牢记在心
...and know his and every other outfits' mission to the detail.
并了解自己其他兵种协同任务的每个细节
Meehan?
米汉中尉?
Yes, Dukeman.
什么事 杜克曼?
Sir, are we dropping tonight?
长官 我们今晚跳吗?
When it's time for you to know, we'll let you know.
该让你知道的时候会告诉你
In the meantime, study these sand tables, maps, and reconnaissance photos...
与此同时 研究这个沙盘地图以及侦察照片
...until you can draw a map of the area by memory.
直到你可以靠记忆画出这一区的地图
Now, we will drop behind this Atlantic wall five hours
我们将在第四步兵师登陆犹他滩头前的五小时
before the 4th Infantry lands at Utah.
降落在这个大西洋防线之后
And between our assembly area and the battalion's objective...
在集结区及空降营目标之间
...there is a German garrison right here in this area, St. Marie du Mont.
这里有个德军的守卫部队 防守着圣梅莉山头
Easy Company will destroy that garrison.
Ｅ连将负责歼灭该军
Three-day supply of K rations, chocolate bars, charms, candy...
三天份的口粮 巧克力棒 精力糖
...powdered coffee, sugar, and matches.
咖啡粉 砂糖跟火柴
Compass, bayonet, entrenching tool, ammunition, gas mask.
罗盘 刺刀 土工器具 弹药 防毒面具
Musette bag with ammo, my webbing, my.45, canteen...
携物袋加预备弹药 我的伪装网 45手枪 水壶
...two cartons of smokes.
两包烟
Hawkins mine, two grenades, smoke grenade, gamma grenade...
霍金式地雷 两枚手榴弹 烟雾弹 伽玛弹
...TNT, this bullshit, and a pair of nasty skivvies.
炸药 这鬼玩意 还有件脏内衣
What's your point?
你到底什么意思?
This weighs as much as I do.
这些东西和我的体重相当
I've still got my chute, my reserve chute, my Mae West, my M-1.
我还要带降落伞 副伞 救生衣 M1步枪
Where are you keeping your brass knuckles?
那你的指节铜套要放哪里?
I could use some brass knuckles.
我或许会用得上指节铜套的
Hey, anything for me?
费斯特 有给我的吗?
No.
没有
Sergeant Martin.
马丁中士
For Talbert.
泰伯特!
Heavy! condoms?
很重呢 保险套吗?
I don't know, probably.
我不知道 也许是吧
What you got?
信上写的什么?
"Dear Floyd: Give them hell."
"亲爱的佛洛依德 让敌人都下地狱"
It's from the chief of the Kokomo Police.
是柯科摩警察局长寄来的
Right.
对
You've got to love cops.
这些警察真是可爱
All right, listen up, listen up.
好了 注意听
If you did not sign your GI life insurance policy...
如果你还没签你的大兵人寿险单
...you go on over and see Sergeant Evans at the headquarters company tent.
现在就去总部连办公室找依凡斯中士
You boys don't let your families miss out on $10,000.
可别让你们的家人平白损失一万元
You hear that, Gerry?
你听到了吗 杰瑞?
Hey, Lip?
李普?
Yeah, boy.
什么事?
Has Guarnere said anything about his brother?
葛奈瑞有告诉你关于他老哥的事吗?
No.
没有
I got a problem.
我们有麻烦了
My wife keeps up with things back home, casualty lists and like that.
我老婆在美国随时注意消息 如阵亡名单
Yeah?
怎么?
Guarnere's brother in Italy?
葛奈瑞的老哥在意大利?
Henry?
亨利?
Killed in Monte Cassino.
在蒙地卡西诺阵亡
Well, I'm sure he doesn't know.
我确定他并不知道
Damn.
糟糕
What'd you think I should do?
你觉得我该怎么做?
If it were me, I'd tell him.
如果是我 我会告诉他
Couple of hours before we jump?
就在跳伞前几小时?
I don't know.
我不知道
Why are they springing these things on us now?
他们干嘛现在把这些东西加挂在我们身上?
It's just an extra 80 pounds strapped to your leg.
多了80磅的重量绑在你的腿上
Does anybody have any idea how the hell this thing works?
有没有知道这鬼玩意儿怎么用?
Colonel Sink.
辛克上校给你的
"Soldiers of the regiment.
团里的各位弟兄:
"Tonight is the night of nights.
今晚就是大战的第一晚
"Today, as you read this...
当你在看这封信时
"...you are en route to the great adventure for which you have trained...
你正踏上前往伟大历险的征途上
"...for over two years."
为此你已受训两年多
So, that's why they gave us ice cream.
那就是为什么给我们冰淇淋吃
Easy Company, listen up!
Ｅ连注意!
Channel coast is socked in with rain and fog.
海峡对岸雨雾弥漫
No jump tonight.
今晚不跳了
The invasion has been postponed.
登陆行动已经延后了
We're on a 24-hour stand-down.
我们现在进入24小时预备状态
Well, this is quite a surprise.
这真是出人意料之外
Not particularly.
倒不见得
It so happens I rather expected it.
既来之则安之
Well, I can't see how you people can pass up $80,000 for the Cause.
我实在无法理解你们 怎能为了八万块钱就从军
For whose cause?
我可不是为钱从军的
If you're so interested in serving a cause...
如果是为了薪给的话
...why don't you join the Army?
为什么不干脆加入陆军算了?
Next, please.
下一位请
Oh, 4F.
我穿4M
You look 1A to me.
你看来像是穿1A号
You don't look so bad yourself.
你本人比较好看
"Dearest Johnny"?
"亲爱的强尼"
Well, should you be giving blood?
你是不是该捐个血?
I woke up.
我醒来了
I got the wrong goddamn jacket.
我穿到别人的外套
I was struck by lightning.
我好象触电一样
Nobody dancing.
没有人在跳舞
It doesn't matter.
没有关系
"Your pal, Bill Guarnere's brother..."
"比尔葛奈瑞的哥哥"
Good luck, lads.
祝你们好运
See you, tommies.
再见了 英国大兵
See you, mate.
帮我修理德国佬
Try and get these leg straps through.
试穿你的脚束
Johnny?
强尼?
Got something you might be looking for.
你大概找这个很久了
Took your jacket by mistake.
我不小心拿错了
I'm sorry.
抱歉
You read it?
你看了吗?
Where the fuck is Monte Cassino?
蒙地卡西诺在哪里?
I don't know. Italy somewhere.
我不知道 意大利某处吧
Sorry about your brother, Bill.
很遗憾听到你哥的消息 比尔
I'm sorry for my ma.
对不起我的妈妈
He was...
我哥...
Let's get this over with.
赶快把伞跳完吧
Bill?
比尔?
I'll meet up with you over there.
我会在那里等你的
Gentlemen, Doc Roe is handing these out for air sickness.
各位 罗医官开了晕机药给大家
Orders are, "Every man takes one now, another, 30 minutes in the air."
规定每人现在吃一颗 升空30分钟后再吃一颗
Lieutenant.
中尉
2nd Platoon, listen up.
第二排注意
Good luck.
祝好运
God bless you.
上帝保佑你们
I'll see you in the assembly area.
我们在集结区再见
If the wire contacts are sensitive, then I think all we should have to do...
如果这很敏感的话 我想我们应该...
Goddamn, Lieb.
可恶 李
That airsick pill is making me loopy.
晕机药害我晕头转向